Thomas Gusewelle

Dallas, TX (979) 219-0103 Thomasgusewelle21@gmail.com www.github.com/gkwmedia

PROFESSIONAL STATEMENT

Five years of experience in the media industry, gaining valuable transferable skills in relationship building, strategic planning, and project management. Strong track record of quick learning and adapting in new and complex situations. Easter to leverage a diverse range of talents in a new and engaging professional setting. Committed to lifelong learning and personal development.

EXPERIENCE

GKW Media, Dallas, TX — Owner

Feb 2017-Present

As the owner of GKW Media I work with clients to complete website designs/development, mobile apps, and audio visual projects.

Lossize.com, Dallas, TX — Founder

March 2022 - Present

Lossize.com is an open source web app designed to allow people to simply and easily track their weight loss journey. It is developed using Next.Js, Tailwind CSS, and Supabase for the backend.

Preston Hollow Presbyterian Church, Dallas, TX — Director of Media and Digital Strategies

Feb 2020 - Present

As the Director of Media I am in charge of every aspect of the church's media and digital life. This includes managing all equipment, large installation projects, volunteers, multiple feature length televised music specials, graphics, and development of the church's website.

Raising Cane, Baton Rouge, LA — *Shift Manager*

September 2015 - September 2019

As a shift manager for Raising Canes I was responsible for the entirety of the restaurant on a shift to shift basis. I was required to manage inventory, labor, profit and loss, training, customer service, crew, and safety. Along with ensuring the success of day to day operations I was responsible for the restaurant's training program and ensuring all crew members were trained correctly and thoroughly.

Education

University of North Texas -Master of Music - May 2021

Louisiana State University - Bachelor of Music - May 2019

Programming Languages

Javascript (ES6, NextJS, React, Node.js) Dart (Flutter) HTML/CSS SQL Typescript

Technologies

AWS
Google Cloud
Framer Motion
Tailwind CSS
Vercel
Git
Riverpod
Webflow

Creative Programs

Adobe Premiere Pro Adobe Photoshop Adobe Lightroom Adobe Indesign Adobe Audition Avid Pro Tools

Other Skills

DSLR cameras Cinema cameras Drone piloting Microsoft Office 365

Professional Skills

Problem solving
Agile
Leadership
Teamwork
Determined
Organization
Time Management
Detail oriented